Miklos Rozsa Papers
Miklos Rozsa Papers
- Film music
  - Scores (bound)
    - Knights of the Round Table, bound reproduction with Rózsa's markings (Oversize 276)
    - Lady on a Train, bound reproduction (Oversize 277)
    - Last Embrace, bound reproduction (Oversize 278)
    - [The] Light Touch, bound reproduction with Rózsa's markings (Oversize 279)
    - [The] Lost Weekend, bound reproduction with handwritten inserts (Oversize 280)
    - Lust for Life, empty binding (Oversize 281)
    - Lust for Life, spiral-bound reproduction (Oversize 282)
    - Lydia, bound reproduction with handwritten inserts (Oversize 283)
    - [The] Macomber Affair, bound handwritten score (Oversize 284)
    - Madame Bovary, bound reproduction (Oversize 285)
    - [The] Man in Half Moon Street, bound reproduction (Oversize 286)
    - Moonfleet, bound reproduction with Rózsa's markings (Oversize 287)
    - Naked City, bound reproduction with Rózsa's markings (Oversize 288)
    - [The] Naked City, spiral-bound reproduction (Oversize 289)
    - [The] Naked City, "Pursuit", spiral-bound reproduction (Oversize 290)
    - [The] Other Love, bound reproduction with Rózsa's markings (Oversize 291)
    - Panther Squadron (Men of the Fighting Lady), bound reproduction with Rózsa's markings (Oversize 292)
    - Plymouth Adventure, bound reproduction (Oversize 293)
    - [The] Power, bound reproduction (Oversize 294)
    - [The] Private Files of J. Edgar Hoover, bound reproduction with handwritten inserts (Oversize 295)
    - [The] Private Files of J. Edgar Hoover, bound reproduction with Rózsa's markings (Oversize 296)
    - [The] Private Life of Sherlock Holmes, bound reproduction with handwritten inserts (Oversize 297)
    - Providence, bound reproduction with Rózsa's markings (Oversize 298)
    - Quo Vadis, bound reproduction (Oversize 299)
    - Quo Vadis, Choral Suite, spiral-bound reproduction (Oversize 300)
    - Quo Vadis, Choral Suite, spiral-bound reproduction (Oversize 301)
    - Quo Vadis, Suite for Orchestra, spiral-bound reproduction; includes "Ave Caesar! (March)," "Romanza," "Arabesque," and "Quo Vadis Domine?" (Oversize 302)
    - [The] Red Danube, bound reproduction with handwritten inserts (Oversize 303)
    - [The] Red House, bound reproduction (Oversize 304)
    - Sahara, bound reproduction (Oversize 305)
    - Secret Beyond the Door, bound reproduction with handwritten inserts (Oversize 306)
    - [The] Seventh Sin, bound reproduction with Rózsa's markings (Oversize 307)
    - So Proudly We Hail, bound reproduction (Oversize 308)
    - Sodom and Gomorrah, bound handwritten score (Oversize 309)
    - Something of Value, bound reproduction with Rózsa's markings (Oversize 310)
    - Song of Scheherazade, bound reproduction (Oversize 311)
    - [A] Song To Remember, bound reproduction (Oversize 312)
    - Spellbound, bound reproduction with Rózsa's markings (Oversize 313)
    - Spellbound Concerto for Orchestra, bound reproduction with Rózsa's markings (Oversize 314)
    - [The] Story of Three Loves (Three Love Stories), bound reproduction (Oversize 315)
    - [The] Strange Love of Martha Ivers, bound reproduction (Oversize 316)
    - That Hamilton Woman (Lady Hamilton), spiral-bound reproduction with Rózsa's markings (Oversize 317)
    - That Hamilton Woman (Lady Hamilton), bound reproduction with handwritten inserts (Oversize 318)
    - Thief of Baghdad Suite, bound reproduction with Rózsa's markings (Oversize 319)
    - Thief of Baghdad, bound reproduction with Rózsa's markings (Oversize 320)
    - Thief of Baghdad, spiral-bound reproduction (Oversize 320.5)
    - Time After Time, bound reproduction (Oversize 321)
    - Time After Time, bound reproduction with Rózsa's markings (Oversize 322)
    - Time Out of Mind, bound reproduction (Oversize 323)
    - [A] Time To Love, bound reproduction with handwritten inserts (Oversize 324)
    - Tip On A Dead Jockey, bound reproduction (Oversize 325)
    - Tribute to a Bad Man, bound reproduction (Oversize 326)
    - [The] V.I.P.s, bound handwritten score (Oversize 327)
    - Valley of the Kings, bound reproduction with Rózsa's markings (Oversize 328)
    - Woman of the Town, bound reproduction (Oversize 329)
    - [A] Woman's Vengeance, bound reproduction (Oversize 330)
    - [The] World, The Flesh and The Devil, bound reproduction (Oversize 331)
    - Young Bess, bound reproduction (Oversize 332)
- Memorabilia
  - Award certificates
    - Academy of Science Fiction Fantasy and Horror Films, Best Music Nominee: Time After Time, 1979 (Box 47)
    - American Hungarian Foundation, Abraham Lincoln Award, 1978 (Box 47)
    - California Federation of Music Clubs, Award, 1952 (Box 47)
    - Chicago Artists Association, Honorary Membership, 1977 (Box 47)
    - City of Los Angeles, Proclamation of Miklos Rózsa Day (Box 47)
    - Critics' Circle Film Section, Music Award, 1988 (Box 47)
    - Decibel d'Or, Providence, 1978 (Box 47)
    - Decibel d'Or, Providence, 1978 (Box 47)
    - Max Steiner Music Society
      - Annual Max Steiner Award, 1994 (Box 47)
      - Hall of Fame Award, 1975 (Box 47)
      - Hall of Fame Award, 1994 (Box 47)
    - Musical Courier, Best Original Score of 1946: The Killers (Box 47)
    - Science Fiction Horror & Fantasy Hall of Fame Award, 1977 (Box 47)
    - University of Southern California, Degree of Doctor of Music, 1988 (Box 47)
    - William Morris Agency, Congratulations on Academy Award of 1945 for Spellbound (Box 47)
  - Award plaques and statues
    - Academy of Motion Picture Arts and Sciences
      - Award Nomination Plaques, 6 plaques (Box 48)
      - Best Music, Scoring of a Dramatic or Comedy Picture: Ben-Hur, 1960 (Oversize 347)
    - Antonio Castillo-Gomez, Plaque honoring 81st birthday, 1988 (Box 49)
    - Audio Engineering Society, Honorary Member, 1960 (Box 49)
    - College of Wooster, Degree of Doctor of Music, 1980 (Box 49)
    - Gold medal in wooden frame (Box 49)
    - Laurel Awards Exhibitor, El Cid: "Love Theme", 1962 (Box 49)
    - Limelight Award, Musical Score, Ben-Hur, 1960 (Box 49)
    - National Academy of Recording Arts and Sciences Nomination for Best Sound Track Album or Recording of Music Score from Motion Picture or Television for Ben-Hur, 1960 (Box 49)
    - National Film Society, Max Steiner Award, 1981 (Box 49)
    - Society for the Preservation of Film Music, Award, 1984 (Box 49)
    - Young Musicians Foundation, Appreciation Award, 1963 (Box 49)
  - Film memorabilia, paper memorabilia, such as music cue sheets and photographs
    - Ben Hur (Box 47)
    - Dead Men Don't Wear Plaid (Box 47)
    - Double Indemnity (Box 47)
    - El Cid (Box 47)
    - Fedora (Box 47)
    - Golden Voyage of Sinbad (Box 47)
    - Jacare (Box 47)
    - King of Kings (Box 47)
    - King's Thief (Box 47)
    - Knights of the Round Table (Box 47)
    - Last Embrace (Box 47)
    - Lost Weekend (Box 47)
    - Private Files of J. Edgar Hoover (Box 47)
    - Private Life of Sherlock Holmes (Box 47)
    - Providence (Box 47)
    - Quo Vadis (Box 47)
    - Thunder in the City (Box 47)
  - Financial documents
    - Apartments (Box 50)
    - Automobile, 1964 Alfa Romeo Giulia TI (Box 50)
    - Automobile, 1968 Lancia Flavia (Box 50)
    - Income Tax, 1969-1977; 9 folders (Box 50)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 50)
  - Legal documents
    - Blumenfeld v. Award Productions Inc. et. Al (Box 50)
    - Lackow v. ASCAP (Box 50)
    - Miscellany (Box 50)
    - Personal (Box 50)
    - United States v. Parke, Austin & Lipscomb, Inc. et. al (Box 50)
  - Miscellany
    - 80th Birthday Gala Papers (Box 51)
    - Address Book (Box 51)
    - Art Collection
      - "Lavinia: Duchess of Bolton" (Box 51)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 51)
      - "Portrait of a Gentleman" (Box 51)
    - Biographical Sketches (Box 51)
    - Calendars, 1985-1986 (Box 51)
    - Credit Cards (Box 51)
    - Discographies (Box 51)
    - Draft Papers (Box 51)
    - Driving Permits (Box 51)
    - Great Hollywood Composers: Míklos Rózsa, 1996; Turner Classic Movies; VHS. (Box 52)
    - Green Card Files, 2 boxes (Box 52)
    - Maps and Travel Guides (Box 52)
    - Medical Documents (Box 53)
    - Passports and Identity Papers (Box 53)
    - Personal Objects (Box 53)
    - Pocket Diaries, 1940; 1943 (Box 53)
    - Poster for Los Angeles performance of Rozsa's double concerto for violin and cello, Louis Kaufmann on violin (Map-case 102)
    - Postcards (Box 53)
    - Scrapbooks
      See also Correspondence-subject files: Rozsa, Regina.
      - Scrapbook (Box 53)
      - Scrapbook (Oversize 341)
      - Scrapbook (Oversize 342)
      - Scrapbook (Oversize 343)
      - Scrapbook (Oversize 344)
      - Scrapbook (Oversize 345)
    - Stationery (Box 54)
    - Travel Receipts (Box 54)
    - Writing Implements (Box 54)
  - Photographs
    - Film Negatives and Slides (Box 54)
    - Film Canisters (Box 55)
    - Photographs, 8 inches x 10 inches and smaller (Oversize 336)
    - Photographs, 8 inches x 10 inches and smaller (Oversize 337)
    - Photographs, 8 inches x 10 inches and smaller (Oversize 338)
    - Photographs, 8 inches x 10 inches and smaller (Oversize 339)
    - Photographs, 8 inches x 10 inches and smaller (Oversize 340)
    - Large matted photographs in box (Oversize 346)
    - Portrait Printing Plate (Box 54)
- Printed material
  - Articles and clippings, 1930-1996; undated
    - 1930-1956, 27 folders (Box 56)
    - 1957-1965, 9 folders (Box 57)
    - 1966-1976, 13 folders (Box 58)
    - 1977-1982, 7 folders (Box 59)
    - 1983-1991, 9 folders (Box 60)
    - 1992-1996, undated, 8 folders (Box 61)
  - Concert programs, 1918-1995; undated
    - 1918-1955, 38 folders (Box 62)
    - 1956-1965, 10 folders (Box 63)
    - 1966-1970, 7 folders (Box 64)
    - 1971-1977, 7 folders (Box 65)
    - 1978-1987, 10 folders (Box 66)
    - 1988-1995, undated, 9 folders (Box 67)
  - Press notices
    - Capriccio, Pastorale e Danza, op. 14 (Box 68)
    - Concert Overture, op. 26 (Box 68)
    - Sonata for Piano, op. 20 (Box 68)
    - Theme, Variations and Finale, op. 13 (Box 68)
    - Viola Concerto, op. 24 (Box 68)
  - Publicity, brochures, press releases; 2 folders (Box 68)
- Commercial recordings
  - Compact discs
    - A History of Hitchcock: Dial M for Murder, Paul Bateman, City of Prague Philharmonic, 1993; Silva Screen Records FILMCD 137 (Box 69)
    - Alfred Hitchcock: Music from His Films, 1999; Museum of Modern Art MM103 (Box 69)
    - Always and Forever: Movies' Greatest Love Songs, John Mauceri, Hollywood Bowl Orchestra, 1996; Philips Classics Productions 446 681-2 (Box 69)
    - Always and Forever: Movies' Greatest Love Songs, John Mauceri, Hollywood Bowl Orchestra, 1996; Philips Classics Productions 446 681-2 (Box 69)
    - An Evening with the Hollywood Bowl Symphony Orchestra, 1995; EMI Classics CDZE 7243 5 68860 2 5 (Box 69)
    - Anniversary Broadcasts 1997 by Matthias Keller, Vol. 2 (Box 69)
    - Béla Bartók, Miklós Rózsa, Peter Csaba, Virtuosi di Kuhmo, 1998; Ondine ODE 919-2 (Box 69)
    - Ben-Hur: Original Motion Picture Soundtrack, 1996; Turner Entertainment 7243 8 52787 2 3 (Box 69)
    - Ben-Hur: The Original Soundtrack Recording, CBS CDCBS 70276 (Box 69)
    - Blood & Thunder: Parades, Processionals and Attacks from Hollywood's Most Epic Films, Cliff Eidelman, Seattle Symphony Orchestra, 1995; Varèse Sarabande Records VSD-5561 (Box 69)
    - Chamber Music, Kaleidoscope, Op. 19b, Sonata for Solo Flute, Op. 39, North Hungarian Peasant Songs and Dances, Op. 5, Sonata for Solo Violin, Op. 40, 1994; Silva Screen Records SILKD 6006 (Box 69)
    - Cinema Café: The European Film Music Album, 1998; Silva Screen Records filmxcd 302 (Box 69)
    - Classic Rózsa, 1988; DRG Records CDSBL 13101 (Box 69)
    - Complete Music from the MGM Presentation of Ben-Hur, 1991; Sony Music Entertainment A2K 47020 (Box 69)
    - Complete Original Film Score to William Wyler's Ben-Hur, Aldebaran 0506095 / 59.1-3 (Box 69)
    - Concert for Violin and Orchestra, Igor Gruppman, James Sedares, New Zealand Symphony Orchestra, 1997; KOCH International Classics 3-7379-2-H1 (Box 69)
    - Concerto for Violin and Orchestra, op. 24, Concerto for Cello and Orchestra, op. 32, Theme and Variations for Violin, Cello and Orchestra, op. 29a, 2000; Telarc Digital CD-80519 (Box 69)
    - Concerto for Violin and Orchestra, op. 24, Concerto for String Orchestra, op. 17, Andante for Strings, op. 22a, 1997; KOCH International Classics 3-7379-2-H1 (Box 69)
    - Concerto for Violin and Orchestra, op. 24, Concerto for String Orchestra, op. 17, Andante for Strings, op. 22a, 1997; KOCH International Classics 3-7379-2-H1 (Box 69)
    - Concerto for Violin and Orchestra, op. 24, Concerto for String Orchestra, op. 17, Andante for Strings, op. 22a, 1997; KOCH International Classics 3-7379-2-H1 (Box 69)
    - Double Indemnity, The Killers, Lost Weekend, James Sedares, New Zealand Symphony Orchestra, 1997; KOCH International Classics 3-7375-2 H1 (Box 69)
    - Double Life, 1990; Bay Cities BCD-1020 (Box 69)
    - Double Life, 1990; Bay Cities BCD-1020 (Box 69)
    - Duo, Op. 7, String Trio, Op. 1, Piano Quintet, Op. 2, Leonard Pennario and Endre Granat, 1988; Cambria Records and Publishing CD-1034 (Box 69)
    - Duo, Op. 7, String Trio, Op. 1, Piano Quintet, Op. 2, Leonard Pennario and Endre Granat, 1988; Cambria Records and Publishing CD-1034 (Box 69)
    - El Cid, 1991; Sony Music Entertainment AK 47704 (Box 69)
    - El Cid, Demo, 1995; Audio Mechanics Music and Sound Restoration (Box 69)
    - El Cid, Demo 2, 1995; Audio Mechanics Music and Sound Restoration (Box 69)
    - El Cid, James Sedares, New Zealand Symphony Orchestra, 1996; KOCH International Classics 3-7340-2H1 (Box 69)
    - El Cid, James Sedares, New Zealand Symphony Orchestra, 1996; KOCH International Classics 3-7340-2H1 (Box 69)
    - Elmer Bernstein, The Magnificent Seven, James Sedares, The Phoenix Symphony, 1994; KOCH International Classics 3-7222-2H1 (Box 69)
    - Epic Film Music of Miklós Rózsa, City of Prague Philharmonic, 1996; Silva Screen Records FILMCD 170 (Box 69)
    - Epic Film Music of Miklós Rózsa, Kenneth Alwyn, City of Prague Philharmonic, 1996; Silva America Digital Film Scores SSD 1056 (Box 69)
    - Epic Film Music of Miklós Rózsa, Kenneth Alwyn, City of Prague Philharmonic, 1996; Silva Screen Records FILMCD 170 (Box 69)
    - Erich Wolfgang Korngold, Miklós Rózsa, 1991; Bay Cities BCD 1032 (Box 69)
    - Fahrenheit 451, Joel McNeely, Seattle Symphony Orchestra, 1995; Varèse Sarabande VSD-5551 (Box 69)
    - Fedora Original Motion Picture Soundtrack, 1989; Varèse Sarabande Records VCL 8903.2 (Box 69)
    - Film Scores of Miklós Rózsa, Angel CDM 7243 5 65993 2 1 (Box 69)
    - Gerard Schurmann, Miklós Rózsa, Cello Concertos, 1996; Silva Screen Records SILKD 6011 (Box 69)
    - Gerard Schurmann, Miklós Rózsa, Cello Concertos, Peter Rejto, Cello, 1996; Equilibrium EQ24 (Box 69)
    - Great Epics, Bill Broughton, Orchestra of the Americas, 1994; Intersound CDB 8403 (Box 69)
    - Great Fantasy Adventure Album, Erich Kunzel, Cincinnati Pops Orchestra, 1994; Telarc Digital CD-80342 (Box 69)
    - Great Waltz, John Mauceri, Hollywood Bowl Orchestra, 1993; Philips Classics Productions 438 685-2 (Box 69)
    - Great Waltz, John Mauceri, Hollywood Bowl Orchestra, 1993; Philips Classics Productions 438 685-2 (Box 69)
    - Heifetz Collection, Volume 21: Korngold, Concerto, op. 35, Rózsa, Concerto, op. 24, Waxman, "Carmen" Fantasy, Heifetz, 1994; BMG Classics BM 610 (Box 69)
    - Herrmann, Sinfonietta for String Orchestra, Waxman, Sinfonietta for String Orchestra & Timpani, Rózsa, Andante for String Orchestra op. 22a, Concerto for String Orchestra, Isaiah Jackson, Berlin Symphony Orchestra, 1992; KOCH International Classics 3-7152-2H1 (Box 69)
    - Hollywood Marches, 1993; BMG Music 09026-61539-2 (Box 69)
    - Hollywood Nightmares, John Mauceri, Hollywood Bowl Orchestra, 1994; Philips Classics Productions 442-425-2 (Box 69)
    - Hollywood Sound: John Williams Conducts the Academy Awards' Best Scores, London Symphony Orchestra, 1997; Sony Classical SK 62788 (Box 69)
    - Hungaria: A Ballet in One Act, Brian Benison, personal CD-R copy (Box 69)
    - Hungarian Sketches: The Miklós Rózsa Collection, 1996; KOCH International Classics 3-7601-2 (Box 69)
    - Ivanhoe, Bruce Broughton, Sinfonia of London, 1994; Intrada MAF 7055D (Box 69)
    - Jazz at the Movies Band, White Heat / Film Noir, 1994; Discovery Records 77008 (Box 69)
    - Julius Caesar, Bruce Broughton, Sinfonia of London and Sinfonia Chorus, 1995; Intrada MAF 7056D (Box 69)
    - King of Kings Original Motion Picture Soundtrack, 1992; Sony AK 52424 (Box 69)
    - King's Thief, Scaramouche, Captain Blood, The Three Musketeers, Richard Kaufman, Brandenburg Philharmonic Orchestra, 1995; HNH International 8.223607 (Box 69)
    - Knight Without Armor, 1994; Intrada MAF 7057D (Box 69)
    - Knight Without Armor, 1994; Intrada MAF 7057D (Box 69)
    - Knights of the Round Table, Original Motion Picture Score, 1982; Varèse Sarabande VCD 47269 (Box 69)
    - Korngold, Violin Concerto, Rózsa, Violin Concerto and Tema con Variazioni, Waxman, "Carmen" Fantasy, Heifetz, 1988; BMG Classics 7963-2-RG (Box 69)
    - Korngold, Violin Concerto, Rózsa, Violin Concerto and Tema con Variazioni, Waxman, "Carmen" Fantasy, Heifetz, 1988; BMG Classics 7963-2-RG (Box 69)
    - Last Embrace Original Motion Picture Score, 1991; Varèse Sarabande Records VCL 9101.9 (Box 70)
    - Legendary Hollywood: Miklós Rózsa, 1997; Citadel Records STC 77111 (Box 70)
    - Leonard Bernstein's New York Philharmonic Debut, New York Philharmonic (Box 70)
    - Leonard Pennario: Film Themes and Variations, 1993; Cambria Records CD-1093 (Box 70)
    - Liszt: Les Préludes, Mazeppa, Hungarian Rhapsodies, Boskovsky, Rózsa, Masur, 1995; EMI Classics CDE 7243 5 69038 2 1 (Box 70)
    - Lost Weekend / Blood on the Sun, Tsunami TSU 0132 (Box 70)
    - Lust For Life Suite, Background to Violence, 1993; Varèse Sarabande Records VSD-5405 (Box 70)
    - Miklós Rózsa at M-G-M, 1999; Turner Entertainment R2 75723 (Box 70)
    - Miklós Rózsa Hollywood Spectacular, Rainer Padberg, Royal Philharmonic Orchestra, 1985; Bay Cities BCD 3028 (Box 70)
    - Miklós Rózsa, Duo, op. 7, Erich Wolfgang Korngold, Sonata in G Major, op. 6, 1991; Bay Cities BCD 1027 (Box 70)
    - Miklós Rózsa: Complete Works for Solo Piano, Sara Davis Buechner, 1999; KOCH International Classics 3-7435-2 H1 (Box 70)
    - Miklós Rózsa: Film Music for Piano, Daniel Robbins, 1994; Intrada MAF 7057D (Box 70)
    - Miklós Rózsa: Film Music for Piano, Volume 2, Daniel Robbins, 1995; Intrada MAF 7064 D (Box 70)
    - Miklós Rózsa: Film Music Vol. #1: Ben Hur, King of Kings, The Power, Prometheus PCD 122 (Box 70)
    - Miklós Rózsa: Film Music Vol. #2: Dead Men Don't Wear Plaid, Prometheus PCD 126 (Box 70)
    - Miklós Rózsa: Hollywood Legend, Elmer Bernstein, Nuremberg Symphony Orchestra, 1989; Varèse Sarabande Records VSD-5206 (Box 70)
    - Miklós Rózsa: The Complete Music for Solo Violin, Variations on a Hungarian Peasant Song, op. 4, North Hungarian Peasant Songs and Dances, op. 5, Duo for Violin and Piano, op. 7, Sonata for Solo Violin, op. 40, 1995; KOCH International Classics, 3-7256-2H1 (Box 70)
    - Miklós Rózsa: The Complete Music for Solo Violin, Variations on a Hungarian Peasant Song, op. 4, North Hungarian Peasant Songs and Dances, op. 5, Duo for Violin and Piano, op. 7, Sonata for Solo Violin, op. 40, 1995; KOCH International Classics 3-7256-2 H1 (Box 70)
    - Miklós Rózsa: The Complete Orchestral Music, Vol. III: Viola Concerto, op. 37, Sinfonia Concertante, op. 29, 1996; KOCH International Classics 3-7304-2H1 (Box 70)
    - Miklós Rózsa: The Complete Orchestral Music, Vol. III: Viola Concerto, op. 37, Sinfonia Concertante, op. 29, 1996; KOCH International Classics 3-7304-2H1 (Box 70)
    - Miklós Rózsa: The Complete Orchestral Music, Vol. IV: Concerto for Piano and Orchestra, op. 31, Concerto for Cello and Orchestra, op. 32, 1998; KOCH International Classics 3-7402-2H1 (Box 70)
    - Modern Masters I: Rózsa, Tripartita for Orchestra, op. 33, Gould, Folk Suite, Menotti, Triplo Concerto a Tre, Lavry, Emek, David Amos, London Symphony Orchestra, 1990; Harmonia Mundi HMU 906010 (Box 70)
    - Modern Masters I: Rózsa, Tripartita for Orchestra, op. 33, Gould, Folk Suite, Menotti, Triplo Concerto a Tre, Lavry, Emek, David Amos, London Symphony Orchestra, 1990; Harmonia Mundi HMU 906010 (Box 70)
    - Music from Hollywood, 1995; Columbia CK 66691 (Box 70)
    - My Kind of Music, Ron Goodwin, Bournemouth Symphony Orchestra, 1989; Chandos Records CHAN 8797 (Box 70)
    - Original Motion Picture Sound Tracks: Quo Vadis, Madame Bovary, Ivanhoe, Plymouth Adventure, 1998; tickertape tt3001 (Box 70)
    - Piano Concerto, op. 31, Cello Concerto, op. 32, Janos Starker, Münchner Philharmoniker, 1986; Pantheon Music International D07124 (Box 70)
    - Piano Works by Miklós Rózsa, Eric Parkin, 1994; Cambria CD-1081 (Box 70)
    - Piano Works by Miklós Rózsa, Eric Parkin, 1993; Cambria CD-1081 (Box 70)
    - Plymouth Adventure (Schiff ohne Heimat) Original Motion Picture Soundtrack, 1999; tickertape tt 3014 (Box 70)
    - Providence Original Motion Picture Soundtrack, 1992; CAM CSE 085 (Box 70)
    - Rhapsody in Blue and Spellbound Concerto, 1995; 3 1/2" floppy for keyboard; Yamaha Corporation of America PSP-1973 (Box 70)
    - Sax and Violence: Music fron the Dark Side of the Screen, 1995; Varèse Sarabande Records VSD-5562 (Box 70)
    - Serenada Hungaria: Dohnányi, Serenade Op. 10; Kodály, Serenade Op. 12; Rózsa, Sonata per Violino Op. 40, 1990; Bayer Records BR 100 058 CD (Box 70)
    - Seventh Sin, Complete Original Film Score of 1957 (Box 70)
    - Sir Malcolm Arnold: Hobson's Choice, St. Clair Trio, 1995; KOCH International Classics - 3-7266-2H1 (Box 70)
    - Sodom and Gomorrah: Original Sound Track Recording, 1990; Cambria Records CD-1050 (Box 70)
    - Sodom and Gomorrah: Original Sound Track Recording, 1990; Cambria Records CD-1050 (Box 70)
    - Solo Sonatas, Opp. 39-42, Bonita Boyd, Charles Neidich, Greg Nestor, Mischa Lefkowitz, 1987; Pantheon/Outlet Book Company D10761 (Box 70)
    - Spectacular Film Music of Miklós Rózsa Volume 3: Young Bess, Prometheus PCD 133 (Box 70)
    - Spectacular Film Music of Miklós Rózsa Volume 3: Young Bess, Prometheus PCD 133 (Box 70)
    - Spectacular Film Music of Miklós Rózsa Volume 4: All The Brothers Were Valiant, Prometheus PCD 131 (Box 70)
    - Spectacular Film Music of Miklós Rózsa Volume 4: All The Brothers Were Valiant, Prometheus PCD 131 (Box 70)
    - Spellbound: The Classic Film Scores of Miklós Rózsa, Charles Gerhardt, National Philharmonic Orchestra, 1990; RCA Victor 0911-2-RG (Box 70)
    - Spellbound: The Classic Film Scores of Miklós Rózsa, Charles Gerhardt, National Philharmonic Orchestra, 1990; RCA Victor 0911-2-RG (Box 70)
    - St. Paul's Christmas Concert, John Scott, Royal Philharmonic Orchestra and St. Paul's Cathedral Choir, 1992; RPO Records CDRPO 7021 (Box 70)
    - String Quartet #1, Op. 22, 1950, String Quarter #2, Op. 38, 1981, Rhapsody for Cello & Piano, Op. 3, 1929, 1988; Laurel Record LR-842CD (Box 70)
    - String Quartet #1, Op. 22, 1950, String Quarter #2, Op. 38, 1981, Rhapsody for Cello & Piano, Op. 3, 1929, 1988; Laurel Record LR-842CD (Box 70)
    - Summon the Heroes, John Williams, Boston Pops Orchestra, 1996; Sony SK 62592 (Box 70)
    - Symphonic Hollywood, Richard Kaufman, Nuremberg Symphony Orchestra, 1991; Varèse Sarabande Records VSD-5329 (Box 70)
    - Symphonic Hollywood, Volume 1, Richard Kaufman, Nürnberger Symphoniker, 1991; Colosseum Schallplatten CST 34.8048 (Box 70)
    - Symphony in 3 Movements, op. 6a, The Vintner's Daughter, op. 23a, James Sedares, New Zealand Symphony Orchestra, 1994; KOCH International Classics 3-7244-2H1 (Box 70)